Conservative Party Archive: Constituency Correspondence CPA CCO 1
Conservative Party Archive
Constituency Correspondence
1936-1971
CPA CCO 1
Conservative Party Archive
4960.0 shelfmarks
Correspondence and memoranda, 1936-1971, with and about individual constituencies.
Organisational History
The Conservative Party Archive (CPA) preserves the records of the Conservative Party’s central and national organisations (primarily what were formerly known before recent changes of name as Conservative Central Office and the National Union of Conservative and Unionist Associations) along with certain regional records. It is recognised by the Conservative Party as the official repository for its historic records and those of affiliated organisations, and receives new material on a regular basis.
The CPA was established as a source for academic study at the Bodleian Library in 1978 by an agreement made between the University of Oxford and the Conservative Party, and brought together surviving historic papers of the Party previously held in various locations including Newcastle University Library and the former Conservative Central Office in Smith Square, London. Since 1996, ownership and financial responsibility for the CPA has been vested in the Conservative Party Archive Trust.
Papers held in the Archive represent all three areas of Party organisation: elected, through the papers of the 1922 Committee, Shadow Cabinet and Chief Whip’s Office; voluntary, through the papers of the National Union of Conservative and Unionist Associations (including its Provincial Councils), and its successor the National Conservative Convention; and professional, through the working files of the Conservative Research Department, Conservative Central Office (including its Area Offices) and its successor, Conservative Campaign Headquarters and their many departments and committees. With few exceptions the Archive does not generally hold the private papers of individuals; rather it holds papers created by them in the course of carrying out their official Party duties.
Although the parliamentary party constitutes the longest-established element of Conservative Party organisation, dating back to the Tory grouping in the House of Commons of the 17th century, the papers of the National Union are by far the oldest in the Archive, with a virtually unbroken series of minutes dating back to 1867. Conservative Central Office was established in 1870, but many records were lost to salvage drives during the War, and a number of moves by Central Office since led to the destruction of still more, particularly from the period before 1939. As a result, the archive consists predominantly of post-Second World War material. The records of the Conservative Research Department, housed separately from Conservative Central Office until 1979, date back to its foundation in 1929.
Scope and Contents note
These files contain correspondence and memoranda with and about individual constituencies. Perhaps the files of greatest interest are those on by-elections. Other items of note are Area agents’ reports on constituency organisation and papers for the selection of parliamentary candidates. Many files contain personal information and Area agents' private assessments of constituency candidates and officers. Access to such files may therefore be restricted. The earliest date from 1936, but most are from the post-war period.
Arrangement note
Central Office filed its papers on individual constituencies in a number of chronological date series, varying between one and six years in length. Within each series constiuencies were listed according to the regional Area in which they were situated. The Areas were given code letters and each consituency was allocated a reference number. This system has been retained in the archive. Because of occasional boundary changes, however, a constituency's number does tend to change from one date series to another. In about 1961 the Party's Area organisation was also altered, so that many constituencies changed Area and several of the Areas changed their code letter. To trace the files on a particular constituency it is necessary to consult the list of files for the appropriate Area in each date series.
Many of the date series are incomplete. Indeed CCO 1/1,1/2, 1/3, 1/4, 1/5, 1/6, 1/13 and 1/15 each contain only a very few surviving files. Few files exist for Northern Ireland constituencies.
Where a town or City contains a number of constituencies it is common for there to be a general file for the town as a whole, in addition to one for each constituency. Such general files are designated by a number made up from the catalogue numbers of its first and last component constituencies. Thus the general file for Nottingham in the date series CCO 1/7 (November 1948-March 1950) is indicated by the number 246/249. When requesting it the full number, CCO 1/7/246/249, should be given. To order the Constituency files within such a town it is necessary to specify them individually. Thus CCO 1/7/246 indicates the Nottingham Central constituency file for the same date series.
Full range of shelfmarks:
CCO 1/1-15
Conditions Governing Access note
General access conditions apply to this material.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The Conservative Party.
Conservative Party; 20th century; Great Britain -- Politics and government -- 20th century
- Constituency files, May 1936-Jun 1937
  Full range of shelfmarks:
  CCO 1/1
  - North Staffordshire Political Union [Comprising:- Stoke-on-Trent, Hanley, Burslem, and Newcastle under Lyme], May 1936-Jun 1937; CCO 1/1/269; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Jul 1937-Jan 1939
  CCO 1/2/269
  - North Staffordshire Political Union [Comprising:- Stoke-on-Trent, Hanley, Burslem, and Newcastle under Lyme], Jul 1937-Jan 1939; CCO 1/2/269; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Jan 1939-Sep 1942
  CCO 1/3/312
  - Rugby By-Election, Jan 1939-Sep 1942; CCO 1/3/312; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Oct 1942-Dec 1945
  CCO 1/4/175/181-CCO 1/4/382
  - Leeds City, Oct 1942-Dec 1945; CCO 1/4/175/181; 1.0 file
  - Huddersfield, Oct1942-Dec 1945; CCO 1/4/182; 1.0 file
  - Worcester, Oct1942-Dec 1945; CCO 1/4/316; 1.0 file
  - Uxbridge, Oct1942-Dec 1945; CCO 1/4/382; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Jan 1946-Aug 1947
  CCO 1/5/63-CCO 1/5/391
  - Jarrow By-Election, Jan 1946-Aug 1947; CCO 1/5/63; 1.0 file
  - Huddersfield, Jan 1946-Aug 1947; CCO 1/5/182; 1.0 file
  - Leeds, Jan 1946-Aug 1947; CCO 1/5/187/192; 1.0 file
  - Cirencester and Tweksbury, Jan 1946-Aug 1947; CCO 1/5/258; 1.0 file
  - North Staffordshire Political Union [Comprising:- Stoke-on-Trent, Hanley, Burslem, and Newcastle under Lyme], Jan 1946-Aug 1947; CCO 1/5/279/280; 1.0 file
  - Bexley, Jan 1946-Aug 1947; CCO 1/5/391; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Sep 1947-Oct 1948
  CCO 1/6/182-CCO 1/6/364
  - Huddersfield, Sep 1947-Oct 1948; CCO 1/6/182; 1.0 file
  - North Staffordshire Political Union [Comprising:- Stoke-on-Trent, Hanley, Burslem, and Newcastle under Lyme], Sep 1947-Oct 1948; CCO 1/6/279/280; 1.0 file
  - Kings Norton By-Election, Sep 1947-Oct 1948; CCO 1/6/364; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Nov 1948-Mar 1950
  - Area A - London, Nov 1948-Mar 1950
    CCO 1/7/1-CCO 1/7/43
    - Battersea North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/1; 1.0 file
    - Battersea South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/2; 1.0 file
    - Bermondsey, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/3; 1.0 file
    - Bethnal Green, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/4; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Dulwich, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/5; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Peckham, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/6; 1.0 file
    - Chelsea, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/7; 1.0 file
    - Cities of London and Westminster, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/8/1; 1.0 file
    - City of London, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/8/2; 1.0 file
    - Abbey, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/8/3; 1.0 file
    - St. George's, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/8/4; 1.0 file
    - Deptford, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/9; 1.0 file
    - Fulham East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/10; 1.0 file
    - Fulham West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/11; 1.0 file
    - Greenwich, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/12; 1.0 file
    - Hackney South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/13; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/14; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith South By-Election, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/15/1; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/15/2; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith South By-Election, Organisation Department file, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/15/3; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith South By-Election - G.D.s file, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/15/4; 1.0 file
    - Hampstead, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/16; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/17; 1.0 file
    - Islington East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/18; 1.0 file
    - Islington North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/19; 1.0 file
    - Islington South West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/20; 1.0 file
    - Kensington North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/21; 1.0 file
    - Kensington South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/22; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Brixton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/23; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Norwood, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/24; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Vauxhall, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/25; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/26; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/27; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/28; 1.0 file
    - Paddington North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/29; 1.0 file
    - Paddington South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/30; 1.0 file
    - Poplar, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/31; 1.0 file
    - St. Marylebone, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/32; 1.0 file
    - St. Pancras North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/33/1; 1.0 file
    - St. Pancras North By-Election, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/33/2; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/34/1; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/34/2; 1.0 file
    - Southwark, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/35; 1.0 file
    - Stepney, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/36; 1.0 file
    - Stoke Newington and Hackney North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/37; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Central, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/38; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Clapham, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/39; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Putney, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/40; 1.0 file
    - [Vacant], [CCO 1/7/41]
    - Woolwich East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/42; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/43/1; 1.0 file
    - University of London, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/43/2; 1.0 file
  - Area B - Northern, Nov 1948-Mar 1950
    CCO 1/7/44-CCO 1/7/77
    - Carlisle, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/44; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Penrith and the Border Division, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/45; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Whitehaven Division, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/46; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Workington, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/47; 1.0 file
    - Darlington, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/48; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/49/50; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/49; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/50; 1.0 file
    - South Shields, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/51; 1.0 file
    - Stockton-on-Tees, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/52; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/53/54; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/53; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/54; 1.0 file
    - The Hartlepools, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/55; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Bishop Aukland, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/56; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Blaydon, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/57; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Chester-le-Street, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/58; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Consett Division, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/59; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Durham Division, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/60; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Easington Division, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/61; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Houghton-le-Spring Division, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/62; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Jarrow Division, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/63; 1.0 file
    - Durham, North West Durham Division, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/64; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Sedgefield Division, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/65; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough East Conservative Association, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/66/67; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/66; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/67; 1.0 file
    - Blyth, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/68; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle on Tyne Conservative Association, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/69/72; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle Central, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/69; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/70; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/71; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/72; 1.0 file
    - Tynemouth, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/73; 1.0 file
    - Wallsend, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/74; 1.0 file
    - Berwick on Tweed, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/75; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle, Hexham, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/76; 1.0 file
    - Northumberland, Morpeth, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/77; 1.0 file
  - Area C - NorthWest, Nov 1948-Mar 1950
    CCO 1/7/78-CCO 1/7/157
    - Altrincham and Sale, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/78; 1.0 file
    - Bebington, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/79; 1.0 file
    - Birkenhead, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/80; 1.0 file
    - Stockport, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/81/82; 1.0 file
    - Stockport North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/81; 1.0 file
    - Stockport South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/82; 1.0 file
    - Wallasey, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/83; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Cheadle, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/84; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, City of Chester, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/85; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Crewe, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/86; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Knutsford, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/87; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Macclesfield, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/88; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Northwich, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/89; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Runcorn, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/90; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Stalybridge and Hyde, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/91; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Wirral, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/92; 1.0 file
    - Accrington, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/93; 1.0 file
    - Ashton-Under-Lyne, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/94; 1.0 file
    - Barrow-in Furness, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/95; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/96/97; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/96; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/97; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/98/99; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/98; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/99; 1.0 file
    - Bolton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/100/101; 1.0 file
    - Bolton East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/100; 1.0 file
    - Bolton West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/101; 1.0 file
    - Bootle, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/102; 1.0 file
    - Burnley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/103; 1.0 file
    - Bury and Radcliffe, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/104; 1.0 file
    - Crosby, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/105; 1.0 file
    - Droylsden, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/106; 1.0 file
    - Eccles, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/107; 1.0 file
    - Leigh, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/108; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/109/117; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Edgehill, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/109; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Exchange, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/110; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Garston, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/111; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Kirkdale, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/112; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Scotland, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/113; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Toxteth, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/114; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Walton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/115; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Wavertree, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/116; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool West Derby, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/117; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/118/126; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Ardwick, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/118; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Blackley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/119; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Cheetham, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/120; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Clayton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/121; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Exchange, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/122; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Gorton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/123; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Moss Side, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/124/1; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Moss Side By-Election, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/124/2; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Withington, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/125; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Wythenshawe, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/126; 1.0 file
    - Nelson and Colne, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/127; 1.0 file
    - Oldham, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/128/129; 1.0 file
    - Oldham East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/128; 1.0 file
    - Oldham West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/129; 1.0 file
    - Preston, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/130/131; 1.0 file
    - Preston North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/130; 1.0 file
    - Preston South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/131; 1.0 file
    - Rochdale, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/132; 1.0 file
    - Rossendale, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/133; 1.0 file
    - St. Helen's, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/134; 1.0 file
    - Salford, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/135/136; 1.0 file
    - Salford East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/135; 1.0 file
    - Salford West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/136; 1.0 file
    - Southport, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/137; 1.0 file
    - Stretford, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/138; 1.0 file
    - Warrington, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/139; 1.0 file
    - Wigan, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/140; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Chorley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/141; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Clithero, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/142; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Darwen, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/143; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Farnworth, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/144; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Heywood and Royton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/145; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Huyton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/146; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ince, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/147; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Lancaster, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/148; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Middleton and Prestwich, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/149; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Morecombe and Lonsdale, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/150; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Newton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/151; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, North Fylde, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/152; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/153; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, South Fylde, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/154; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Westhoughton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/155; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Widnes, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/156; 1.0 file
    - Westmorland, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/157; 1.0 file
  - Area D - Yorkshire, Nov 1948-Mar 1950
    CCO 1/7/158-CCO 1/7/213
    - Barnsley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/158; 1.0 file
    - Bately and Morley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/159/1; 1.0 file
    - Bately and Morley By-Election, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/159/2; 1.0 file
    - Bradford, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/160/163; 1.0 file
    - Bradford Central, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/160; 1.0 file
    - Bradford East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/161; 1.0 file
    - Bradford North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/162; 1.0 file
    - Bradford South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/163/1; 1.0 file
    - Bradford South - By-Election, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/163/2; 1.0 file
    - Bradford South - By-Election, Organisation Department file, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/163/3; 1.0 file
    - Bradford South- By-Election, Mr Garmonsway's file, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/163/4; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse and Spenborough, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/164/1; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse and Spenborough - By-Election, G.D.'s file, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/164/2; 1.0 file
    - Dews Bury, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/165; 1.0 file
    - Doncaster, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/166; 1.0 file
    - Halifax, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/167; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/168/169; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/168; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/169; 1.0 file
    - Keighley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/170; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/171/174; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Central, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/171; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/172; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Haltemprice, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/173; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/174; 1.0 file
    - Leeds, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/175/181; 1.0 file
    - Leeds Central, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/175; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/176; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/177; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/178; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/179; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South East, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/180; 1.0 file
    - Leeds West, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/181/1; 1.0 file
    - Leeds West By-Election, Organisation Department file, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/181/2; 1.0 file
    - Leeds West By-Election, G.D.'s file, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/181/3; 1.0 file
    - Pontefract, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/182; 1.0 file
    - Pudsey, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/183; 1.0 file
    - Rotherham, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/184; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/185/191; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Attercliffe, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/185; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Brightside, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/186; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Hallam, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/187; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Healey, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/188; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Hillsborough, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/189; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Neepsend, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/190/1; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Neepsend By-Election, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/190/2; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield Park, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/191; 1.0 file
    - Wakefield, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/192; 1.0 file
    - York, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/193; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Barkston Ash, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/194; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Beverley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/195; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Bridlington, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/196; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Cleveland, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/197; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Colne Valley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/198; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Dearne Valley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/199; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Don Valley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/200; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Goole, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/201; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Harrogate, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/202; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Hemsworth, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/203; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Normaton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/204; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Penistone, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/205; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Richmond, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/206; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Rippon, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/207; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Rother Valley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/208; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Scarborough and Whitby, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/209; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Shipley, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/210; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Skipton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/211; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Sowerby, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/212; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Thirsk and Malton, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/213/1; 1.0 file